Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art registrar's office records, 1869-2013 COR0005.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reproduction rights and photo orders [legacy series], 1963-1980; Series 5
  - Graphic Arts Unlimited, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Graham Gallery, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Groiler Inc., 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Guidance Associates, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Holt, Rinehart & Winston, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - I MIscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - J - K Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Love Galleries, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - L MIscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Michigan Artrain Inc., 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Mondadori Publishing Co., 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Morse, John D. (Thru Harry Abrams), 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Ma - Mc Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Me - Mu Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - National Historical Society, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Te Neus Verlag (Germany?), 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Platt, Frederick, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - P MIscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Readers Digeest, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Smithsonian - NCFA, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Smithsonian - Nat'l Gallery of Art, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Smithsonian - Nat'l Portrait Gallery, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - S MIscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - UNICEF, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - U.S. Defense Dept., 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - U.S. Historical Society, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - U.S. Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - University of MIssouri, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Universities A - Z, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Watson-Guptill Publications, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Wellesley College, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - John Wiley & Sons, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - W MIscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Y Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Zauho Press, 1978; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Albany County Historical Association, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - American Art & Antiquities, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Arete Publishing Co., 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Arts Magazine, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - A - Am Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - An - Az Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Cornell University, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Fabbri Editori, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich Inc., 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Haverstock, Mary, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - H MIscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - I - K Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - London Regional Art Gallery, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Main Street Press, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - Musical Heritage Society, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Pa Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Po Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - Pr Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Ra - Re Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Ro - Ru Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Science Press, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - Silver Burdett Co., 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Smithsonian - NCFA, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 190)
  - Smithsonian - Nat'l Gallery of Art, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - Smithsonian - Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - S MIscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - Thames & Hudson Ltd, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - T MIscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Univ. of Chicago Press, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - Univ. of Connecticut, 1979; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 197)
  - Univ. of South Carolina, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Viking Penguin Inc., 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Watson-Guptill Publications, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Whitney Museum of Art, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Women Artists, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - W MIscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Z MIscellaneous, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - C MIscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - D MIscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ginn & Co., 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Harper & Row Co., 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - William Heinemann Ltd., 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Hirschl & Adler, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - I MIscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Laidlaw Brothers, 1988; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - M - R Miscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Scholastic Magazines, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - S MIscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - U MIscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - V - W MIscellaneous, 1980; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Victor Amato - Photography Aagreement w/ CGA, 1963; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - American Archives of World Art / Redbook, 1964-1965; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Chadwick Healey Ltd., 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Field Educational PUblications, 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Arthur A. Kaplan Co., 1967-1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Media Presidentations, 1967-1968; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Media Presentations - Gloege Productions, 1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Media Presentations - Holt, Rinehart &Winston, 1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Media Presentations - Keyboard, 1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Media Presentations - Project 7 Productions, 1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Media Presentations - U.S. State Dept., 1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Media Presentations, 1970; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Media Presentations, 1971; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Media Presentations, 1975; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Media Presentations - ABC Mews, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Media Presentations - BBC, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Media Presentations - Catonsville Community College, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Media Presentations - Field Enterprises, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Media Presentations - Guidance Associates, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Media Presentations - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Media Presentations - Media Generalists, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Media Presentations - Miniature Gallery, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Media Presentations - No. Virginia Community College, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Media Presentations - Weiner, Steven H., 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Media Presentations - WQUED Public TV, 1976; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Media Presentations - Albany (NY) Bicentennial, 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Media Presentations - Butterick, 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Media Presentations - Filmedia, 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Media Presentations - Historical Society of Passy: Auteuil Registrars Office, 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Media Presentations - Miami Dade Community College, 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Media Presentations - Niagra Falls Heritage Foundation, 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Media Presentations - Shoshana (Producer), 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Media Presentations - WETA, 1977; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Media Presentations - BBC, 1978; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Media Presentations - Granada Television, 1978; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Media Presentations - Minnesota Historical Society, 1978; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Media Presentations - Nat'l Geographic Society, 1978; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Media Presentations - WNET TV, 1978; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Media Presentations - BBC, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Media Presentations - Flying Cimarron Productions, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Media Presentations - Historical Society of Passy: Auteuil Registrars Office, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Media Presentations - Maryland St. Dept. of Education, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Media Presentations - Mininberg, Ian, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Media Presentations - National Geographic Society, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Media Presentations - Tourtelot, Madeline, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Media Presentations - Visual Education, 1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - New York Graphic Society, 1967; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Sandak Slides Project: Corres. & Memos, 1965-1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Sandak Slides Project:: Corres. & Memos, 1970-1975; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Sandak Slides Project: Invoices & Purchase Orders, 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Sandak Slides Project: Lists of Works of Art, 1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Shorewood Press "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" Corres., 1963; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Shorewood Press "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" Corres., 1965; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" Corres., 1966; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" Corres., 1967; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" Corres., 1968; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" Lists of Works of Art, nd; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" - Pilgrim Investigation: Dateline, Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" - Pilgrim Investigation Pt. 1, nd; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" - Pilgrim Investigation Pt. II, nd; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" - Pilgrim Investigation Pt. III, nd; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Shorewood "American Masterpieces / Favorite Amer. Paintings" Misc. Notes on, nd; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Shorewood Publishers "Private World of J.S. Sargent", 1963-1969; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Shorewood Publishers- MIsc. Projects, 1977-1979; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - State University of New York at Binghamton - Photo Order, 1969-1970; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Winterthur Museum, 1967-1970; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Misc. Reproduction Fee Schedules, nd; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 88)
- Reproduction rights and photo orders, 1979-1987; Series 13
  Additional reproduction rights and photo order files are located in Series 5 Reproduction rights and photo orders [legacy series], 1963-1980.
  This series contains correspondence and order forms for reproduction requests received by the Corcoran Gallery of Art, which were transferred to the Corcoran Archives following the original Corcoran Archives processing project in 1983.
  - Bi-monthly paid photo bills, 1979-1987; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Completed Photo Orders, 1981 May-July; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Completed Photo Orders, 1981 August-December; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Photography - Pending Correspondance Requests for Information, etc, 1982 September-1983 February; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1982 February-1980 October; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1983 March-December; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1984 January 1-November 28; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Misc., circa 1986; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1985 November 1-1986 November 1; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1986 November-1987 August 31; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1987 September 1-December; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1989 January 1-June 30; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Photo Orders Completed, 1986 April 1-October 31; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Photo Orders Completed, 1986 November-1987 March; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Photo Orders Completed, 1987 March-October; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Photo Orders, 1980; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Completed Photo Orders, 1980 January-June; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Completed Photo Orders, 1980 September-December; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Completed Photo Orders, 1981 January-April; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Photo Order Memos, circa 1980; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Bequests, 1884-1979; Series 6
  Materials are arranged chronologically by bequest date.
  The series consists of catalogs, correspondence, lists of bequeathed materials, meeting minutes, memoranda, shipping orders and receipts, and wills/will codicils on works of art bequeathed to the Corcoran. Major bequests appearing in the series include Bradley, Clark, New York Studio School, and the Tayloe Collection.
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Bill of Sale (From E. Thornton Tayloe to Phebe Tayloe), 1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Bill os Sale 26 Oct. 1878 (From Tayloe to CGA), 1878-1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Committee Meeting Minutes, 1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Committee Report on Tayloe Collection 1891, 1884-1891; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Correspondence (Misc.), 1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Expenses on Moving Collection, 1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Will, 1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Will Excerpt, 1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Tayloe, Phebe W.: Miscellaneous, 1884; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Lemon, George E., 1898; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Stevens, Elizabeth S., 1919; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Bradley, George L. & Helen: Catalogs, 2nd set, 1920; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Bradley, George L. & Helen: Catalogs (Paper copies), 1920; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Bradley, George L. & Helen: Committee (Trustee) Meeting 5/11/19, 1919 May 11; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Bradley, George L. & Helen: Committee (Trustee) Meeting 5/22/19, 1919 May 22; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Bradley, George L. & Helen: List of Works of Art in Collection, 1920; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Bradley, George L. & Helen: Will of George L., 1920; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Bradley, George L. & Helen: Will of Helen McHenry, 1920; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Oyster, George M., Jr., 1924; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreements (Legal) Master List, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreement #2, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreement #3, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreement #4, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreement #5, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreement #6, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Clark, Sen. William A. :Agreement #7, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreement #8, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Agreement #9, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Annual Report of Operation of Clark Wing & Collection, 1947-1965; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Biography of Clark, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Building Addition "Clark Wing" - Trustee Resolutions, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Building Addition - Fund - Receipts & Ledger Info., 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Building Addition - Fund - Receipts Cont., 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Catalog, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Clark Additional Maintenance Fund, 1925-1959; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Clark Additional Maintenance Fund, 1960-1964; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Clark Collection Antiquities Catalog, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Clark Collection Antiquities Catalogs, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Clark Collection Antiquities Catalog - Original 1911, Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Clark Collection Ceramics (Vases, Statuettes) Catalog, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Clark Fund - Works of Art urchased from, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Inspection of Works, Notes, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: List of Works of Art, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Loan Policy for Collection, 1958; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Meeting Minutes (Trustees), 1925 April-1925 June; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Meeting Minutes (Trustees), 1925 July-1925 October; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Meeting Minutes (Trustees), 1925 November; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Meeting Minutes, 1926 January-1926 March; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Meeting Minuters, 1926 April-1926 October; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Meeting Minutes, 1927; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Metropolitan Museum of Art (NY) - Refusal of Collection, 1925; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: New York Trips for Collection Inspection - Reports, 1925; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Operating Reception for Clark Collection, 1928; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Packing/Moving - List of Works of Arts, 1925; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Publicity, 1925; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Tablet, 1925; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Will Extracts, 1925; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Clark, Sen. William A.: Miscellaneous, 1925; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Wittelsey, Elisha, 1927; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Maxwell, Mary E. & Memorial Fund, 1927; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Stevens, Joseph Sampson [1 of 2], 1935; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Stevens, Joseph Sampson [2 of 2], 1935; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder data_value_missing_cd7ef3b57c2c8c5934f1b447785eca62)
  - Walker, Edward C. & Mary: Condition of Works Report, 1937; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Walker, Edward C. & Mary: Lists of Works of Art, 1937; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Walker, Edward C. & Mary: Will, 1937; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Walker, Edward C. & Mary: MIscellaneous, 1937; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - White, Grace Hoffman, 1937; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Garfinkel, Julius, 1938; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - White, Amelia Elizabeth, 1938; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Stuart Farrar, 1939; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Shirlaw, Mrs. Walter 1930's?, 1930-1939; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Parmelee, James: Last Will & Testament (Pluss Codicils), 1926-1927; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Parmelee, James: Lists of Works of Art, 1940; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Parmelee, James: Lists of Works of Art Cont., 1940; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Parmelee, James: Legal Document [1 of 2], 1940; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Parmelee, James: Legal Document [2 of 2], 1940; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Parmelee, James: Receipts of Works of Art Ackowledgement, 1940; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Parmelee, James: Schedule of Stock Distribution of, 1940; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Steinmetz, Clara W. M., 1941; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Ormond, Violet (Sargent Drawings), 1949; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Smithers, Mabel S. (Mrs. Francis S.), 1952; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Keyes, Bessie Potter Vennoh: Appraisal of Collection, 1955; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Keyes, Bessie Potter Vennoh: Receipt of Collect. Acknowl., 1955; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Keyes, Bessie Potter Vennoh: MIsc. Lists of Works, 1955; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Levinson, Annie F., 1959; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Clark, Anna E. (Stradavaris) - Correspond. Regarding, 1963-1964; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Clark Anna E. (Stradavaris) - Will, 1963-1964; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Stewart, Marguerite (Mrs. James F.M.), 1963-1964; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Halpert, Edith G.: Agreements of Gift 1962 Revoked 1968, 1962-1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Halpert, Edith G.: Agreements of Gift 1964 Revoked 1968, 1964-1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Halpert, Edith G.: Agreements of Gift 1965-66 Revoked 1968, 1965-1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Halpert, Edith G.: Lists of Works of Art Revoked 1968, 1965-1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Halpert, Edith G.: MiscellaneousRevoked 1968, 1965-1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Briston, Frank: Corresp. Regarding, 1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Briston, Frank: List of works of Art, 1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Bristow, Frank: Will, 1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Tuttle, Gertrude, 1968; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Wagner, Clarissa Edmonston, 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Rosenberg, James, 1969; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Bode, Helen Spaulding: Appraisal of Collection, 1971-1972; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Bode, Helen Spaulding: Will, 1971-1972; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Garrett, Ethel S. (Mrs. George A.), 1972; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 50)